Emmanuel! (God with us - Matthew 1:23)
Praise God!
My testimony is this:
My name is Mata Williams.
I am 54 years old.
I am a mother of six children.
I am from Bradford, UK.
I was going up to Glasgow from Bradford to hear my daughter in a performance.
It's five hours by train.
This was on January 22nd, 2011.
The next day as I was travelling back, at 4pm I started feeling violently sick;
I was vomiting and having diarrhoea for five hours.
I vomited all the way down to Bradford.
By the time I arrived there, I was very weak.
I thought that maybe it had finished, that I couldn't vomit anymore
and that there was nothing left in my body.
Then when I went home to lie down, a new case of vomiting started.
This time it felt as if my intestines were coming out of my body
and I didn't know what to do.
It was 12 midnight, so I called my children to bring me my laptop.
I knew I was dying but I thought at least let me find somebody who could pray for me.
So, I told them to find 'Christian healing'.
When they searched on YouTube, Prophet T.B. Joshua's face appeared.
He then started praying; he prayed very strongly.
As he prayed, my body started to shake.
Then he said, "Touch the screen". So I touched the screen,
and my body was going crazy in the bed.
Then after that...
I knew that I couldn't get to a hospital because there wasn't enough time;
I knew that I was actually dying and this was the only chance that I had to live.
God was speaking to me that I needed to be prayed for.
As the prophet was praying for me, I didn't know who this person was.
He was just praying strongly.
After that, he said to me, "Get up!"
He told everybody to 'Get up!'.
So, I got out of my bed and then I felt some stregnth come inside my body
and this huge monster or whatever it was, leaving me.
I was surprised because I had been lying in bed all this time, I couldn't move
but then through the internet, Prophet T.B. Joshua was telling me
to get out of bed, to 'Get up'.
So, I got up, went to the bathroom and looked at my face.
I had lost so much weight from my body.
I looked at my face and I saw the mask of a skeleton.
I then realised that this life and death situation was just by the grace of God...
Through this man of God, I am alive today.
I never saw him before in my life.
The next day, I got my children to find out who he is, where he's from, what's his church.
They found out he is in Nigeria.
So I thought, "I want to go and thank him".
I thank God for this.
I am indebted to God and to Prophet T.B. Joshua that I am alive today.
It's a very big privilege.
Have you listened to that?
Through YouTube.
Just like that.
She never knew that this was from Nigeria.
But after the prayer, the solution came,
and she then said, "Let me look for (this church)".
That's all - YouTube!
Glory be to God!
So, thank you.
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe to witness more of God’s power at work in our generation today
and stay up-to-date with the latest prophecies, deliverances,
sermons and testimonies from The SCOAN.
Emmanuel TV – Changing Lives, Changing Nations and Changing the World.